<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Phonetics | Hywel Stoakes</title>
    <link>https://academic-demo.netlify.app/tag/phonetics/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://academic-demo.netlify.app/tag/phonetics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Phonetics</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2022 Hywel Stoakes</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://academic-demo.netlify.app/media/icon_hua2ec155b4296a9c9791d015323e16eb5_11927_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Phonetics</title>
      <link>https://academic-demo.netlify.app/tag/phonetics/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Major Rebuild</title>
      <link>https://academic-demo.netlify.app/post/a-major-rebuild/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://academic-demo.netlify.app/post/a-major-rebuild/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;script src=&#34;https://academic-demo.netlify.app/post/a-major-rebuild/index.en_files/header-attrs/header-attrs.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


&lt;p&gt;I realised a few months back that my personal website had stopped updating and that I needed to put in some work to get it back up and running. In addition, my domain name had expired and I had no idea how to migrate without some serious headaches. I revived the domain name, but realised the version of the site that was served was seriously out of date. It was an entirely static site and the pipeline I was using to update the content had stopped updating. In the interim I have moved institution and country and I came to the conclusion that I needed to either pull the site or update it with a more modern architecture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I needed a plan to either migrate to a new site and recreate the posts or patch together what I already had. Most of my previous site was used as a place to store some of my papers rather than used as a blogging platform. I have never been a very diligent blogger and have often left sites languishing preferring to create new sites rather than updating old content. &lt;a href=&#34;https://hywel.github.io&#34;&gt;See this old github site&lt;/a&gt; which is now broken completely apart from the twitter feed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really didn’t want to move away from using Blogdown to update the site because I am so heavily invested in the &lt;strong&gt;R&lt;/strong&gt; ecosystem and most of my analysis work uses it and Rmarkdown. I thought I would document a couple of the steps I took in the rebuild. In essence I just backed up and then deleted the site and re-downloaded the Hugo Academic template, adding in old posts and content very carefully. Most of the installation information below come directly from &lt;a href=&#34;https://bookdown.org/yihui/blogdown/&#34;&gt;the blogdown book&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&#34;r&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;## Install from CRAN
install.packages(&amp;#39;blogdown&amp;#39;) 
## Or, install from GitHub
if (!requireNamespace(&amp;quot;devtools&amp;quot;)) install.packages(&amp;#39;devtools&amp;#39;)
devtools::install_github(&amp;#39;rstudio/blogdown&amp;#39;)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I then updated Hugo from within Rstudio&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&#34;r&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;blogdown::update_hugo()&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the version of Hugo that I am running:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&#34;r&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;blogdown::hugo_version()&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;## [1] &amp;#39;0.92.0&amp;#39;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is the theme that I ended up using, which is an update of the original theme. And this is the command I used to install it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&#34;r&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;blogdown::new_site(theme = &amp;#39;wowchemy/starter-academic&amp;#39;)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a fair bit of customisation that needs to be done in the &lt;code&gt;config/_default&lt;/code&gt; folder and the &lt;code&gt;content/home&lt;/code&gt; folder. This is where you can choose to remove pages and content. The documentation is fairly easy to follow (&lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I use &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.netlify.com&#34;&gt;Netlify&lt;/a&gt; to serve the site as recommended by Yihui Xie and Blogdown. This seems to be fairly stable and I can get Netlify to build the site using Hugo in only a couple of seconds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;blogdown-version&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;blogdown version:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yihui Xie (2020). blogdown: Create Blogs and Websites with R Markdown. R package version 0.21.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vowel Duration and Consonant Lengthening in Djambarrpuyngu</title>
      <link>https://academic-demo.netlify.app/publication/conference-paper/2019-05-29-vowel-duration-and-consonant-lengthening-in-djambarrpuyngu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://academic-demo.netlify.app/publication/conference-paper/2019-05-29-vowel-duration-and-consonant-lengthening-in-djambarrpuyngu/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;script src=&#34;index_files/header-attrs/header-attrs.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;link href=&#34;index_files/anchor-sections/anchor-sections.css&#34; rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; /&gt;
&lt;script src=&#34;index_files/anchor-sections/anchor-sections.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
